[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Wait a minute, wait a minute, you aint heard nothin yet. is a quote from this first feature-length talkie, produced by Warner Bros.", "correct_answer": "The Jazz Singer", "incorrect_answers": ["Applause", "Movietone", "Blackmail"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The most common  fossil is the tooth.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What large and obvious summer asterism do Vega, Deneb, and Altair form?", "correct_answer": "Summer Triangle", "incorrect_answers": ["Summer Cross", "Summer Hex", "Summer Pyramid"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Smooth strokes are enhanced by this substance, which is often used during a massage.", "correct_answer": "Oil", "incorrect_answers": ["Butter", "Spirits", "Powder"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happens to the shark at the end of the 1975 movie Jaws.", "correct_answer": "It is killed", "incorrect_answers": ["It escapes", "They find out it is pregnant", "Non of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Luxembourg was not involved in any 20th century war.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many species of rhinoceros survive in the wild?", "correct_answer": "5", "incorrect_answers": ["2", "4", "3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the last statement made by Alex at the end of the 1971 Stanley Kubrick movie A Clockwork Orange?", "correct_answer": "I was cured, all right!", "incorrect_answers": ["Everything looks blurred...", "Nothing on this planet is what it seems to be.", "I see the tunnel clearly now."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which of these movies has actor Gerard Butler appeared prior to The Ugly Truth?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["RocknRolla", "300", "The Phantom of the Opera"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What important internal organ does the ostrich lack?", "correct_answer": "Gallbladder", "incorrect_answers": ["Liver", "Spleen", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first mathematician to use the term group?", "correct_answer": "Evariste Galois", "incorrect_answers": ["Georg Cantor", "Augustin Cauchy", "Leonhard Euler"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What city did the Indianapolis Colts move from in 1984?", "correct_answer": "Baltimore", "incorrect_answers": ["Boston", "New England", "Los Angeles"]}]